{
    "subject": "James_Poe",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Barbara_Steele",
    "human_readable": "James Poe is married to Barbara Steele.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9852370619773865,
            "question": "Are James Poe and Barbara Steele married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9118009805679321,
            "question": "To whom is Barbara Steele married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8451621532440186,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between James Poe and Barbara Steele?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8261957168579102,
            "question": "Who is James Poe married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104746341705322,
            "question": "Who are James Poe and Barbara Steele?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7188325524330139,
            "question": "Name the wife of James Poe."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7179991602897644,
            "question": "Does James Poe have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6459775567054749,
            "question": "What is the name of Barbara Steele's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251800417900085,
            "question": "Is James Poe in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28241580724716187,
            "question": "Is Barbara Steele single?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Poe is married to Barbara Steele.",
            "html": "yago_15702_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is James Poe in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_15702_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Barbara Steele's husband?",
            "html": "yago_15702_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does James Poe have a spouse?",
            "html": "yago_15702_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15702_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indicate that James Wilber Poe was indeed married to actress Barbara Steele from 1969 to 1978, and they had a child together. Therefore, the statement \"James Poe is married to Barbara Steele\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}